{
    "id": "18b301bb26ca4902b52d944737f8e593",
    "title": "Find the mistake â€“ perfect tenses",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "99f958c7b9d24773a20ae96e210e2cb6",
            "title": "Perfect Tenses Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "We .................................. in this city since",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "live",
                        "lived",
                        "have lived"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Tom ................................. with us for ten years before he joined another company.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "work",
                        "had worked",
                        "has worked"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "How long ........................................ with your current employer?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "are you working",
                        "have you been working",
                        "were you working"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ..................................... that novel ten times in my life.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "read",
                        "have read",
                        "am reading"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ........................................... him for ten years.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "knew",
                        "know",
                        "have known"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have known him for several years. I first ................................... him in London.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "meet",
                        "met",
                        "have met"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where have you been since I last ................................ you?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "see",
                        "saw",
                        "have seen"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ..................................... to be an actor since she was a child.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "wanted",
                        "has wanted",
                        "wants"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ..................................... to London in",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "go",
                        "went",
                        "had gone"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She .................................. in three films. Her first film came in",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "acted",
                        "has acted",
                        "acts"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}